Guide to the News Service Biographical Files, circa 1930s - 2004 UA.27.01.0003
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Buettner-Janusch, John (Box 7)
- Buettner-Janusch, John (Box 147)
- Buettner-Janusch, John (Box 65)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Primate Center
- Bufkin, Je Harned (Box 125)
- Bufkin, Je Harned (Box 65)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Medical Record Library
- Bugg, Everett I. (Box 125)
- Bugg, Everett I. (Box 65)
- Bulger, Roger J. (Box 125)
- Bulger, Roger J. (Box 65)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Allied Health Sciences
- Bullock, S. Elizabeth "Betty" (Box 125)
- Bullock, S. Elizabeth "Betty" (Box 147)
- Bullock, S. Elizabeth "Betty" (Box 65)
- Bumbalough, Paul (Box 65)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Office of Student Development
- Burdick, Donald Smiley (Box 125)
- Burdick, Donald Smiley (Box 65)
- Burford, Walter (Box 65)
- Burford, Walter (Box 125)
- Burger, James (Box 65)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Arts and Sciences of Statistics
- Burger, Michael J. (Box 7)
- Burger, Paula (Box 65)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Vice Provost for Academic Services
- Burger, Peter (Box 65)
- Burger, Robert M. (Box 65)
- Burger, Robert M. (Box 125)
- Burger, Wilbert (Bud) E. (Box 7)
- Burger, Wilbert (Bud) E. (Box 125)
- Burgess, Mary (Box 7)
- Burgess, Mary (Box 66)
- Burgess, Mary (Box 125)
- Burgess, Mary (Box 147)
- Burgess, Wade William (Box 66)
- Burian, Peter H. (Box 66)
- Burk, Lawrence (Box 66)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Radiology
- Burke, James R. (Box 66)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Neurology
- Burke, Marian C. (Box 125)
- Burke, Marian C. (Box 66)
- Burkholder, C.I. (Box 125)
- Burkholder, C.I. (Box 147)
- Burkholder, Peter M. (Box 7)
- Burkholder, Peter M. (Box 125)
- Burkholder, Peter M. (Box 66)
- Burlak, Jacob (Box 7)
- Burness, John (Box 66)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Sr. Vice President for Public Affairs
- Burness, John F. (Box 125)
- Burns, Barbara (Box 66)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Psych. and Behavioral Sciences
- Burton, Claude S. (Box 66)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Dermatology, Medicine
- Burton, Richard M. (Box 125)
- Burton, Richard M. (Box 66)
- Busse, Ewald, 5 folders (Box 7)
- Busse, Ewald William (Box 125)
- Busse, Ewald William (Box 66)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Psychiatry and Dean Effective 9/1/1987
- Butler, Edmund (Box 7)
- Butler, Joseph D. (Box 7)
- Butler, Joseph D. (Box 125)
- Butler, Joseph D. (Box 66)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Facility Planning, Retired 5/1985
- Butterfield, Barbara S. (Box 7)
- Butters, Ronald R. (Box 125)
- Butters, Ronald R. (Box 66)
- Butters, Tom A. (Box 125)
- Butters, Tom A. (Box 66)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Athletic Director
- Buzzard, Gale Herbert, II (Box 125)
- Buzzard, Gale Herbert, II (Box 66)
- Byers, Michael (Box 66)
- Byrd, Robert L. (Box 66)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Byrne, William L. (Box 66)
- Byrne, William L. (Box 125)
- Byrne, William L. (Box 147)
- Caddell, Elinor (Box 7)
- Cadell, Elinor (Box 66)
- Cady, Edwin Harrison (Box 7)
- Cady, Edwin Harrison (Box 125)
- Cady, Edwin Harrison (Box 66)
- Cahoon, John (Box 147)
- Cahoon, John B., Jr. (Box 7)
- Cahoon, John B., Jr. (Box 125)
- Cahoon, John B., Jr. (Box 147)
- Cahoon, John B., Jr. (Box 66)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Radiologic Technology
- Cahow, Clark R. (Box 66)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Registrar and of Admissions and Financial Aid
- Cairns, Michael (Box 7)
- Cairns, Michael (Box 66)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Infectious Diseases
- Caldwell, David S. (Box 66)
- Caldwell, Herschel (Box 125)
- Caldwell, Herschel (Box 147)
- Caldwell, Herschel (Box 66)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Football Coach; Coach, Freshman Football, Baseball, and Basketball
- Caldwell, John Tyler (Box 111)
  Biographical information. Alumnus; Chancellor, NCSU
- Caldwell, Sam (Box 147)
- Caldwell, Sam Johnson (Box 125)
- Caldwell, Sam Johnston (Box 7)
- Califf, Robert M. (Box 66)
- Calkins, Philip B. (Box 7)
- Calloway, J. Lamar (Box 66)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Dermatology, died 1/19/1993
- Callcott, Wilfrid H. (Box 7)
- Calloway, J. Lamar (Box 7)
- Calloway, J. Lamar (Box 125)
- Cameron, E.M. (Box 8)
- Cameron, Edmund McCullough "Eddie" (Box 66)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Coach and Athletic Director, died 11/25/1988
- Campbell, Bill (Box 111)
  Biographical information. Alumnus, Law; Mayor, Atlanta
- Campbell, Dennis Marion (Box 125)
- Campbell, Dennis Marion (Box 66)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Divinity School
- Campbell, Janet (Box 8)
- Campbell, Jerry Dean (Box 66)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: University Librarian
- Campbell, Mary B. (Box 8)
- Campbell, Mary B. (Box 125)
- Campbell, Mary B. (Box 66)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Anesthesia
- Campbell, Michael Ian (Box 8)
- Campbell, Richard T. (Box 8)
- Campbell, Sullivan Graham (Box 8)
- Campbell, Ted Allen (Box 66)
- Camporesi, Enrico M. (Box 8)
- Canent, Ramon V., Jr. (Box 66)
- Canine, William (Box 8)
- Cannon, Charles Albert (Box 125)
- Cannon, Charles Albert, Trustee (Box 115)
- Cannon, James, III (Box 66)
- Cannon, James, III (Box 8)
- Cannon, James, III (Box 125)
- Cannon, William R. (Box 125)
- Cannon, William R., Trustee (Box 115)
- Canon, David T. (Box 66)
- Cant, Nell Beatty (Box 66)
- Canterbury, Alfrod K., Jr. (Box 66)
- Cantor, Murray (Box 66)
- Capp, M. Paul (Box 8)
- Capp, M. Paul (Box 125)
- Capp, M. Paul (Box 147)
- Carbone, Peter Francis, Jr. (Box 125)
- Carbone, Peter Francis, Jr. (Box 66)
- Card, Wilbur Wade (Box 8)
- Carden, Norman F., Jr. (Box 8)
- Carin, Lawrence (Box 66)
- Carl, Linda (Box 126)
- Carl, Linda (Box 66)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Cultural Affairs
- Carlitz, Leonard (Box 8)
- Carlson, Alan (Box 66)
- Carlson, Cathy (Box 66)
- Carlton, John W. (Box 8)
- Carmon, Ziv (Box 66)
- Caron, Marc G. (Box 126)
- Caron, Marc G. (Box 66)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Cell Biology
- Carpenter, David Williams (Box 8)
- Carpenter, David Williams (Box 126)
- Carpenter, David Williams (Box 147)
- Carpenter, Dwight W. (Box 8)
- Carpenter, Dwight William (Box 66)
- Carpenter, James M. (Box 8)
- Carr, John W., Jr. (Box 8)
- Carrington, Paul DeWitt (Box 126)
- Carrington, Paul DeWitt (Box 66)
- Carroll, Barbara A. (Box 66)
- Carroll, Bernard J. (Box 66)
- Carroll, Charles F. (Box 111)
- Carroll, Christopher R. (Box 66)
- Carroll, Gilbert (Box 8)
- Carroll, Jackson W. (Box 8)
- Carroll, Jackson W. (Box 126)
- Carroll, Jackson W. (Box 66)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Ormond Center; Divinity School
- Carroll, Malcolm E. (Box 8)
- Carroll, Robert S. (Box 8)
- Carson, Culley C., III (Box 66)
- Carson, Robert Charles (Box 126)
- Carson, Robert Charles (Box 66)
- Carswell, George Harrold (Box 111)
  Biographical information. Alumnus; Judge
- Carter, Allan M. (Box 147)
- Carter, Bayard, 2 folders (Box 8)
- Carter, Bayard (Box 126)
- Carter, Bayard (Box 147)
- Carter, James G. (Box 8)
- Carter, James G. (Box 126)
- Carter, James Henry (Box 126)
- Carter, James Henry (Box 66)
- Carter, Reginald D. (Box 126)
- Carter, Reginald D. (Box 66)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Clinical Physician's Program
- Cartmill, Matt (Box 66)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Departments of Anthropology and Anatomy
- Cartter, Allan Murray (Box 8)
- Cartter, Allan Murray (Box 126)
- Cartwright, William H. (Box 126)
- Cartwright, William H. (Box 147)
- Cartwright, William H. (Box 66)
- Caserta, Ernesto Giuseppe (Box 67)
- Casey, H. Craig (Box 126)
- Casey, H. Craig (Box 67)
- Casey, Patrick J. (Box 67)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Pharmacology and Cancer Biology
- Casseday, John H. "Pete" (Box 67)
- Castellano, Juan R. (Box 8)
- Castellano, Juan R. (Box 147)
- Castriota, David (Box 67)
- Cate, Thomas R. (Box 67)
- Cathcart, A.M. (Box 8)
- Cato, Allen E. (Box 67)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Clinical Pediatrics
- Cattell, Raymond Bernard (Box 8)
- Cavaliere, A. Ralph (Box 8)
- Cavanaugh, G.S. Terrence (Box 126)
- Cavanaugh, G.S. Terrence (Box 67)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Trent Collection, Medied Ctr. Library; Medical Literature
- Cavanaugh, G.S. Terrence (Box 8)
- Cavanaugh, Patrick J. (Box 8)
- Cavanaugh, Patrick J. (Box 67)
- Cavanaugh, Patrick J. (Box 126)
- Cavenar, Jesse O. (Box 67)
- Cavers, David F. (Box 8)
- Cell, John W. (Box 67)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: History, died 10/26/2001
- Cerveris, Michael Edward (Box 67)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Institute of the Arts
- Chaddock, Jack Bartley (Box 126)
- Chaddock, Jack Bartley (Box 147)
- Chaddock, Jack Bartley (Box 67)
- Chafe, William (Box 126)
- Chafe, William (Box 147)
- Chafe, William (Box 67)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: History; TCAS, 1970s-2000s
- Chaffin, Nora Campbell (Box 8)
- Chaiken, Leon Edward (Box 8)
- Chaiken, Leon Edward (Box 126)
- Chaiken, Leon Edward (Box 67)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Forestry Management
- Chamberlain, Hope Summerell (Box 8)
- Chambers, John (Box 112)
  Biographical information. Alumnus; President and CEO Cisco
- Chambers, Julius, Trustee (Box 115)
- Chambers, Robert Luther (Box 8)
- Chamis, Anna Lisa, 2001 (Box 67)
- Champagne, Mary (Box 67)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Nursing School
- Chandler, John Wesley (Box 67)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Univ. Board of Trustees
- Chao, Nelson (Box 67)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Medicine; Bone Marrow Transplant Program, 1998
- Chapman, Norman B. (Box 8)
- Chapman, Norman B. (Box 126)
- Chapman, Norman B. (Box 147)
- Chapman, Robert G. (Box 8)
- Chapman, Roger C. (Box 126)
- Chapman, Roger C. (Box 147)
- Chapman, Roger C. (Box 67)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Forest Biometrics, Appt. 9/1969
- Chappell, Fred (Box 112)
  Biographical information. Alumnus; Poet
- Charles, Hal Cecil (Box 67)
- Charlesworth, James H., 2 folders (Box 9)
- Charlesworth, James H. (Box 67)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Religion
- Charlesworth, James H. (Box 126)
- Chase, Beatrice (Box 126)
- Chase, Beatrice (Box 67)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Nursing, Retired 8/31/1989
- Chase, Jeffrey S. (Box 67)
- Chase, Lewis (Box 9)
- Chatrath, Prithijit (Box 67)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Curator, Primate Center
- Chavis, Benjamin (Box 112)
  Biographical information. Alumnus, Divinity School
- Cheek, Dennis J. (Box 67)
- Cheek, Mrs. Roma S. (Box 9)
- Cheek, Roma S. (Box 126)
- Cheek, Roma S. (Box 67)
- Cheifetz, Ira M. (Box 67)
- Chen, Yuan-Tsong (Box 67)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Genetics and Metabolism, Pediatrics
- Cheney, Margaret (Box 9)
- Chernoff, Amoz I. (Box 9)
- Cherny, Walter (Box 9)
- Cherny, Walter (Box 126)
- Cherny, Walter (Box 147)
- Cherny, Walter B. V. (Box 67)
- Cherpack, Clifton (Box 9)
- Cherpack, Clifton (Box 126)
- Cherpack, Clifton (Box 147)
- Cherpack, Clifton Cyril (Box 67)
- Cherry, R. G. (Box 126)
- Cherry, R. G., Trustee (Box 115)
- Cherry, Robert Stephen (Box 67)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Mechanical and Biomedical Engineering
- Chesnut, Donald Blair (Box 126)
- Chesnut, Donald Blair (Box 67)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Chemistry, (Effective 1/1/1999)
- Childs, Benjamin Guy, 2 folders (Box 9)
- Childs, Benjamin Guy (Box 126)
- Childs, Benjamin Guy (Box 147)
- Childs, Benjamin Guy (Box 67)
- Childs, Carol (Box 67)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Dance Program
- Childs, Jack Stith (Box 67)
- Childs, Jack Stith (Box 126)
- Childs, Sue (Box 67)
- Ching, Leo (Box 67)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Asian and African Language and Literature
- Chiorazzi, Michael G. (Box 126)
- Chiorazzi, Michael G. (Box 67)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Law Library
- Chowdhury, Shyamal (Box 67)
- Christ, Robert W. (Box 9)
- Christakos, Arthur Chris (Box 126)
- Christakos, Arthur Chris (Box 67)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Obstetrics and Gynecology; Medical Education
- Christensen, Norman Leroy (Box 126)
- Christensen, Norman Leroy (Box 67)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Forestry; Angier B. Duke Scholarship Program
- Christian, Charles, II (Box 67)
- Christian, Charles Donald (Box 126)
- Christian, Charles Donald (Box 67)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Obstetrics and Gynecology; Division of Gynecologic Endocrinology
- Christian, Charles, II (Box 9)
- Christie, George C. (Box 126)
- Christie, George C. (Box 67)
- Christmas, William A. (Box 67)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Student Health Services
- Chua, Amy L. (Box 67)
- Church, Austin H. (Box 9)
- Church, Austin H. (Box 126)
- Church, Margaret (Box 9)
- Church, Margaret (Box 126)
- Cianciola, George (Box 67)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Medical Research Prof.
- Cianciolo, George (Box 9)
- Ciompi, Giorgio, 2 folders (Box 9)
- Ciompi, Giorgio (Box 126)
- Ciompi, Giorgio (Box 147)
- Ciompi, Giorgio (Box 67)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Music. Ciompi Quartet
- Clack, Ronald James (Box 67)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: CAPS; Interim Student Affairs (effective 7/1/2000)
- Clapp, James Robert (Box 67)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Medicine; Vice Chancellor, DUMC
- Clark, Bobby Wayne (Box 67)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: University Relations
- Clark, Edgar William (Box 9)
- Clark, Elizabeth Ann (Box 67)
- Clark, Elon (Box 126)
- Clark, Elon (Box 147)
- Clark, Elon Henry (Box 67)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Medical Art, died 1/19/2001
- Clark, Henry Baisley (Box 126)
- Clark, Henry Baisley (Box 147)
- Clark, Henry Baisley (Box 67)
- Clark, Howard G., III (Box 126)
- Clark, Howard G., III (Box 67)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Biomedical and Biochemical Engineering
- Clark, James S. (Box 67)
- Clark, Kenneth Willis, 2 folders (Box 9)
- Clark, Kenneth Willis (Box 126)
- Clark, Kenneth Willis (Box 147)
- Clark, Kenneth Willis (Box 67)
- Clark, Lelia (Box 9)
- Clark, Lelia (Box 147)
- Clark, Peter Barton (Box 67)
- Clark, Reese Hunter (Box 67)
- Clark, Robert E. (Box 67)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Dermatologic Surgery and Cutaneous Oncology
- Clark, Robert W. (Box 9)
- Clark, Romane Lewis (Box 126)
- Clark, Romane Lewis (Box 147)
- Clark, Romane Lewis (Box 67)
- Clarke, Austin Chesterfield (Box 67)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Black Studies
- Clarke, Edmund Melson, Jr. (Box 9)
- Clarke, George Elliott (Box 67)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: English and Canadian Studies
- Clarke, Maurice (Box 9)
- Clarke-Pearson, Daniel (Box 67)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Gynecologic Oncology
- Clarke-Pearson, Daniel L. (Box 10)
- Clausen, Joy Carol Princeton (Box 10)
- Clavien, Pierre-Alain (Box 67)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: General Surgery
- Clay, Captain Alfred Thomas (Box 10)
- Clay, Diskin (Box 67)
- Clay, Russell Travis (Box 126)
- Clay, Russell Travis (Box 67)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Duke News Service
- Clay, Susan (Box 10)
- Clayton, Robert Brown (Box 126)
- Claytor, Robert Brown (Box 147)
- Claytor, Robert Brown (Box 67)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Divinity School; Chaplain, Medied Center
- Cleaveland, Fred N. (Box 147)
- Cleaveland, Frederic N. (Box 126)
- Cleaveland, Frederic N. (Box 68)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Political Science, Effective 9/1/1985
- Clegg, Scott T. (Box 67)
- Clegg, W. L. (Box 126)
- Clegg, W. L., Trustee (Box 115)
- Cleland, James T., 5 folders (Box 10)
- Cleland, James T. (Box 126)
- Cleland, James T. (Box 147)
- Cleland, James T. (Box 68)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Duke Univ. Chapel; Divinity School, died 11/14/1978
- Cleland, William (Box 68)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Pediatrics, 2001
- Clements, Fiona Marshall (Box 68)
- Cleveland, Louise (Box 10)
- Cleveland, William Porter, Jr. (Box 10)
- Clifford, Edward (Box 68)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Medical Psychology and Research
- Clifford, Paul (Box 10)
- Clifford, Paul (Box 126)
- Clifford, Paul (Box 68)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Pre-Columbian Art Collection, Retired 12/1981
- Clippinger, Frank W., Jr. (Box 68)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Orthopedic Surgery; Rehabilitation Center
- Clogan, Paul Maurice (Box 10)
- Clotfelter, Charles T. (Box 126)
- Clotfelter, Charles T. (Box 68)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Public Policy; Economics, 1980-2001
- Clotfelter, James (Box 68)
- Clough, Gerald Wayne (Box 126)
- Clough, Gerald Wayne (Box 147)
- Clough, Gerald Wayne (Box 68)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Engineering
- Clower, Virginia L. (Box 68)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Psychiatry; Clinical Division of Child Psychiatry
- Clubbe, John (Box 10)
- Clubbe, John Louis Edwin (Box 126)
- Clubbe, John Louis Edwin (Box 147)
- Clubbe, John Louis Edwin (Box 68)
- Clugston, George Alan (Box 10)
- Clum, John MacKenzie (Box 126)
- Clum, John MacKenzie (Box 148)
- Clum, John MacKenzie (Box 68)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: English; Drama, 1960s-2000
- Clyde, Paul (Box 10)
- Clyde, Paul Hibbert (Box 126)
- Clyde, Paul Hibbert (Box 148)
- Clyde, Paul Hibbert (Box 68)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Far East History, died 5/1/1998
- Coats, A. W. (Box 68)
- Cobb, Clarence Harper (Box 10)
- Cobb, Frederick R. (Box 68)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Cardiology; Radiology
- Cobo, L. Michael (Box 68)
- Coburn, Andrew S. (Box 68)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Earth and Ocean Sciences, 2001
- Cochran, George (Box 68)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Center on Law and Poverty
- Cocke, Norman A. (Box 148)
- Cocke, Norman A. (Box 126)
- Cocke, Norman A., Trustee (Box 115)
- Cocks, Franklin Hadley (Box 68)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Mechanical Engineering and Materials Science
- Cocowitch, Harry M. (Box 126)
- Cocowitch, Harry M. (Box 68)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Naval Science Dept., Retired 7/1/1972
- Coder, David (Box 68)
- Coffey, Charles Edward (Box 68)
- Coffman, Thomas M. (Box 68)
- Cohen, Harvey Jay (Box 126)
- Cohen, Harvey Jay (Box 68)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Center for the Study of Aging and Human Development
- Cohen, Kalman J. (Box 126)
- Cohen, Kalman J. (Box 68)
- Cohen, Louis D. (Box 10)
- Cohen, Louis David (Box 126)
- Cohen, Louis David (Box 68)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Psychology, Resigned 1962
- Cohen, Sanford I. (Box 10)
- Cohen, Sanford I. (Box 126)
- Cohen, Sanford I. (Box 68)
- Cohen, Sanford I. (Box 148)
- Cohn, Jonathan A. (Box 68)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Medicine, Cell Biology
- Coie, John David (Box 68)
- Coile, Theodore (Box 148)
- Coile, Theodore Stanley (Box 10)
- Coker, Jerry (Box 126)
- Coker, Jerry (Box 68)
- Cole, R. Taylor, 3 folders (Box 11)
- Cole, R. Taylor (Box 126)
- Cole, T. Boyce (Box 68)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Otolaryngology, Surgery
- Coleman, Dorian Lambelet (Box 68)
- Coleman, Edward (Box 68)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Radiology, 2001
- Coleman, James E., Jr. (Box 68)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Law, 2001
- Coleman, Ralph Edward (Box 68)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Radiology; Nuclear Medicine
- Coleman, Rosalind A. (Box 68)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Genetics and Metabolism, Pediatrics; Biochemistry
- Coles, Robert (Box 68)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Institute of Political Science and Public Affairs
- Coles, Romand (Box 68)
- Collins, Daniel W. (Box 126)
- Collins, Daniel W. (Box 68)
- Collins, Jeffrey Jay (Box 126)
- Collins, Jeffrey Jay (Box 68)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Experimental Surgery, Microbiology and Immunology
- Collins, Leslie M. (Box 68)
- Collins, Sheila (Box 68)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Psychiatry and Pharmacology
- Colton, Joel (Box 126)
- Colton, Joel (Box 148)
- Colton, Joel (Box 68)
- Colver, Robert Merle (Box 11)
- Colver, Robert Merle (Box 126)
- Colver, Robert Merle (Box 148)
- Colver, Robert Merle (Box 68)
- Colvin, O. Michael (Box 68)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Medicine; Cancer Research; Comprehensive Cancer Center
- Conant, Norman F. (Box 11)
- Conant, Norman F. (Box 126)
- Conant, Norman F. (Box 148)
- Conant, Norman F. (Box 68)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Microbiology, died 4/1984
- Conaway, Mark R. (Box 68)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Biometry Division
- Conner, William E. (Box 11)
- Conners, Carmen Keith (Box 68)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Medical Psychology, Psychiatry
- Connery, Robert H. (Box 11)
- Connery, Robert H. (Box 126)
- Connery, Robert H. (Box 68)
- Connolly, John L., Jr. (Box 68)
- Connor, W. Robert (Box 68)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Classical Studies; National Humanities Center
- Conover, Christopher (Box 68)
- Conover, Richard M. (Box 11)
- Conrad, Cecilia (Box 11)
- Conrad, Cecilia (Box 68)
- Conrad, Robert (Box 11)
- Conrad, Robert (Box 126)
- Conrad, Robert Franklin (Box 68)
- Constant, Frank Woodbridge (Box 11)
- Constanzo, Philip R. (Box 69)
- Convery, Frank J. (Box 11)
- Cook, Clark Curtis (Box 11)
- Cook, Philip Jackson (Box 69)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Economics and Public Policy
- Cook, Samuel DuBois (Box 11)
- Cook, Samuel DuBois, 1993 (Box 69)
- Cook, Samuel DuBois (Box 126)
- Cook, Samuel DuBois, 1994-, Trustee (Box 115)
- Cook, Samuel DuBois, Trustee 1981-1993 (Box 115)
- Cook, Wesley A. (Box 69)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Neurosurgery
- Cook-Degan, Robert M. (Box 69)
- Cooke, Miriam (Box 69)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Asian and African Languages, 2001
- Cooke, Wilhelmina R., Trustee (Box 115)
- Coombs, John W. "Jack" (Box 126)
- Coombs, John W. "Jack" (Box 69)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Baseball
- Coombs, John Wesley, 2 folders (Box 11)
- Coon, Susan L. (Box 126)
- Coon, Susan L. (Box 69)
- Cooney, James P. (Box 11)
- Cooney, James P. (Box 69)
- Coonrad, Raphael W. "Ralph" (Box 69)
- Cooper, A. Derwin (Box 69)
- Cooper, Gregory J. (Box 69)
- Cooper, Sherri (Box 69)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: NSOE, 1998
- Cooper, Walter G. (Box 126)
- Cooper, Walter G. (Box 148)
- Cooper, Walter G. (Box 69)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Commanding Officer, V-12, died 9/1991
- Corbett, W. Horace (Box 11)
- Corbin, Charlotte (Box 126)
- Corbin, Charlotte (Box 69)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Alumnae Affairs
- Cordle, Thomas H. (Box 69)
- Corey, Gordon Ralph (Box 69)
- Corker, Lottie C. (Box 11)
- Corless, Joseph M. (Box 69)
- Corless, Roger (Box 126)
- Corless, Roger (Box 69)
- Corliss, Bruce H. (Box 69)
- Correll, Donovan S. (Box 11)
- Corrie, Bruce A. (Box 11)
- Corrie, Bruce A. (Box 126)
- Corrie, Bruce A. (Box 148)
- Corrie, Bruce A. (Box 69)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Lacrosse
- Costello, Elizabeth (Box 69)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Psychiatry and Behav. Sciences
- Costello, Martin J. (Box 69)
- Costlow, John D. (Box 126)
- Costlow, John D. (Box 69)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Marine Lab, 1 of 4
- Cotanch, Patricia H. (Box 11)
- Cotanch, Patricia H. (Box 126)
- Cotton, Peter B. (Box 69)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Gastroenterology
- Cotton, William J.H. (Box 11)
- Counce, Sheila (Box 69)
- Council, C. T., Trustee (Box 115)
- Council, C.T. (Box 126)
- Coury, Louis A., Jr. (Box 69)
- Covi, Dario (Box 69)
- Covi, Dario (Box 126)